"	PU	O	B_CLS
ชัยทิพย์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
"	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ลิ่ว	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัด	VV	O	I_CLS
หวด	VV	O	I_CLS
ดัน	NN	O	I_CLS
ลอป	NN	O	E_CLS

ชาย	NN	O	B_CLS
เดี่ยว	VV	O	I_CLS
รอบ	NN	O	I_CLS
ก่อน	PS	O	I_CLS
รอง	NN	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
เลิศ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สรวงศ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เพ็งทอง	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พลิก	VV	O	I_CLS
เอา	VV	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
มือ	NN	O	I_CLS
วาง	VV	O	I_CLS
อันดับ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ของ	PS	O	I_CLS
รายการ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รภัสสรณ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พิทักษ์พรพัลลภ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
ตลาด	NN	B_LOC	I_CLS
มหาชัย	NN	E_LOC	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2-1	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เซต	CL	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2-5	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-3	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-1	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เข้า	AV	O	I_CLS
ไป	AV	O	I_CLS
เจอ	VV	O	I_CLS
กับ	PS	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ศิริวัฒน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เอส	NN	I_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
มงคลสวัสดิ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
อุทยานแห่งชาติ	NN	B_LOC	E_CLS
อ่าว	NN	I_LOC	I_CLS
มะ	NN	I_LOC	I_CLS
นาว	NN	I_LOC	I_CLS
-	NN	I_LOC	I_CLS
เขา	NN	I_LOC	I_CLS
ตันหยง	NN	E_LOC	I_CLS
_	PU	O	O
ที่	CC	O	B_CLS
หวด	VV	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ธนา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ธรรมเพชร	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
ปราจีนบุรี	NN	B_LOC	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
3-6	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
(	PU	O	I_CLS
7-5	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
)	PU	O	E_CLS

ส่วน	CC	O	B_CLS
อีก	AJ	O	I_CLS
สาย	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เชตวัน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โตวิจักษณ์ชัยกุล	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เข้า	VV	O	I_CLS
รอบ	NN	O	I_CLS
แบบ	NN	O	I_CLS
เสีย	VV	O	I_CLS
เหงื่อ	NN	O	I_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
มาก	VV	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
เมื่อ	CC	O	B_CLS
คู่แข่ง	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชูศักดิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ธรรมเพชร	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ขอ	VV	O	I_CLS
ยอม	VV	O	I_CLS
แพ้	VV	O	E_CLS
เพราะ	CC	O	B_CLS
หายใจ	VV	O	I_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
ทัน	VV	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
หลัง	CC	O	B_CLS
ตาม	VV	O	I_CLS
อยู่	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
1-5	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นพพล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เข้า	AV	O	I_CLS
ไป	AV	O	I_CLS
เจอ	VV	O	I_CLS
กับ	PS	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
วรวงศ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ยี	NN	I_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทองศรี	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
บาง	NN	B_LOC	E_CLS
แสน	NN	E_LOC	I_CLS
_	PU	O	O
ที่	CC	O	B_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ศาสตรา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ตันติไพบูลย์ธนะ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
วัด	NN	B_LOC	I_CLS
ไตรภูมิ	NN	E_LOC	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-1	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-2	NU	B_NUM	E_CLS

ส่วน	CC	O	B_CLS
ใน	PS	O	I_CLS
ประเภท	NN	O	I_CLS
หญิง	NN	O	I_CLS
เดี่ยว	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รอบ	NN	O	I_CLS
ก่อน	PS	O	I_CLS
รอง	NN	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
เลิศ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ประสาท	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สท้อนดี	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นัก	FX	O	I_CLS
หวด	VV	O	I_CLS
สาว	NN	O	I_CLS
วัด	NN	B_LOC	I_CLS
ปากน้ำ	NN	E_LOC	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ไล่	VV	O	I_CLS
ต้อน	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สุขสมรวย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
กำเนิดผล	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
น้ำตก	NN	B_LOC	I_CLS
ตาด	NN	I_LOC	I_CLS
หลวง	NN	E_LOC	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-1	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-1	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เข้า	AV	O	I_CLS
ไป	AV	O	I_CLS
เจอ	VV	O	I_CLS
กับ	PS	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นิกร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ศรีปราชญ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
หาด	NN	B_LOC	E_CLS
ใน	NN	I_LOC	I_CLS
เพลา	NN	E_LOC	I_CLS
_	PU	O	O
ที่	CC	O	B_CLS
เฉือน	VV	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
โสภณ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สัพโส	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-0	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
4-6	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-2	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
วราวุธ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วิริยะโรจน์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ยำใหญ่	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ณัฐวุฒิ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทองหนัก	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-0	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-1	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เข้า	AV	O	I_CLS
ไป	AV	O	I_CLS
พบ	VV	O	I_CLS
กับ	PS	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อนุชา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สินธุไพร	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
สุพรรณบุรี	NN	B_LOC	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
ที่	CC	O	B_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เฉลิมชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แสงดี	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-0	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
7-5	NU	B_NUM	E_CLS



