ศาล	NN	O	B_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
ให้	CC	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
"	PU	O	I_CLS
82	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
กระทรวง	NN	B_ORG	E_CLS
การคลัง.	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS

พร้อม	CC	O	B_CLS
ร้อง	VV	O	I_CLS
ศาล	NN	O	I_CLS
ค้าน	VV	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	I_CLS
กลัว	VV	O	I_CLS
หลบหนี	VV	O	E_CLS

ขณะ	CC	O	B_CLS
ที่	CC	O	I_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ราย	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ขอ	VV	O	I_CLS
ยื่น	VV	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	E_CLS
แต่	CC	O	B_CLS
ศาล	NN	O	I_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
อนุญาต	VV	O	E_CLS

ตาม	PS	O	B_CLS
คำ	NN	O	I_CLS
ร้อง	VV	O	I_CLS
ระบุ	VV	O	I_CLS
ว่า	CC	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
คดี	NN	O	I_CLS
เจ้าหน้าที่	NN	O	I_CLS
ตำรวจ	NN	O	I_CLS
สามารถ	AX	O	I_CLS
จับกุม	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	I_CLS
ได้	AX	O	I_CLS
พร้อม	VV	O	I_CLS
ของกลาง	NN	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
อาทิ	CC	O	B_CLS
_	PU	O	O
อาวุธ	NN	O	B_CLS
ปืน	NN	O	I_CLS
พก	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
3	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
กระบอก	CL	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พร้อม	VV	O	I_CLS
เครื่อง	NN	O	I_CLS
กระสุน	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มีด	NN	O	I_CLS
ดาบ	NN	O	E_CLS
และ	CC	O	B_CLS
มีด	NN	O	I_CLS
ปลาย	NN	O	I_CLS
แหลม	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
วิทยุ	NN	O	I_CLS
สื่อสาร	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
หนังสติ๊ก	NN	O	I_CLS
พร้อม	VV	O	I_CLS
กระสุน	NN	O	I_CLS
ลูก	NN	O	I_CLS
หิน	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
ของกลาง	NN	O	I_CLS
อื่น	AJ	O	I_CLS
ๆ	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
25	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รายการ	CL	O	E_CLS

ต่อมา	CC	O	B_CLS
ทนายความ	NN	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
พรรประชาธิปัตย์	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
ได้	AX	O	I_CLS
ยื่น	VV	O	I_CLS
คำ	NN	O	I_CLS
ร้อง	VV	O	I_CLS
พร้อม	VV	O	I_CLS
หลักทรัพย์	NN	O	I_CLS
เป็น	VV	O	I_CLS
เงินสด	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	O	I_CLS
ละ	AJ	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
แสน	NN	O	I_CLS
บาท	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
ขอ	VV	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นาย	NN	B_TTL	I_CLS
ก่อแก้ว	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พิกุลทอง	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
แกนนำ	NN	O	I_CLS
โรงพยาบาล	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
บางรัก	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
คน	NN	O	I_CLS
จน	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
กับ	PS	O	I_CLS
นาย	NN	B_TTL	I_CLS
จิตติพจน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จินตะเวช	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
13	NU	B_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
14	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อย่างไรก็ตาม	CC	O	I_CLS
ขณะนี้	NN	O	I_CLS
อยู่	VV	O	I_CLS
ระหว่าง	PS	O	I_CLS
รอ	VV	O	I_CLS
ศาล	NN	O	I_CLS
พิจารณา	VV	O	I_CLS
ไต่สวน	VV	O	I_CLS
พนักงาน	NN	O	I_CLS
สอบสวน	VV	O	E_CLS

ศาล	NN	O	B_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
ให้	CC	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
"	PU	O	I_CLS
82	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สน.	NN	B_ORG	E_CLS
คลองตัน	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS

ต่อมา	CC	O	B_CLS
เวลา	NN	B_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
20.30	NU	I_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
น.	CL	E_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ศาล	NN	O	I_CLS
มี	VV	O	I_CLS
คำสั่ง	NN	O	E_CLS
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
พิเคราะห์	VV	O	I_CLS
แล้ว	AX	O	I_CLS
เห็น	VV	O	I_CLS
ว่า	CC	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	B_CLS
ทั้ง	AJ	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
82	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ร่วม	VV	O	I_CLS
กัน	PR	O	I_CLS
ก่อ	VV	O	I_CLS
ความ	FX	O	I_CLS
วุ่นวาย	VV	O	I_CLS
ใน	PS	O	I_CLS
บ้านเมือง	NN	O	E_CLS
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
บุกรุก	VV	O	I_CLS
เข้า	AV	O	I_CLS
ไป	VV	O	I_CLS
ใน	PS	O	I_CLS
โรงเรียน	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
ศรีพฤกฒา	NN	E_ORG	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
ใช้	VV	O	I_CLS
กำลัง	NN	O	I_CLS
ประทุษร้าย	VV	O	E_CLS
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
มี	VV	O	I_CLS
อาวุธ	NN	O	I_CLS
ใน	PS	O	I_CLS
เวลา	NN	O	I_CLS
กลาง	NN	O	I_CLS
คืน	NN	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
อีก	CC	O	B_CLS
ทั้ง	CC	O	I_CLS
ยัง	AX	O	I_CLS
ข่มขืนใจ	VV	O	I_CLS
เจ้าหน้าที่	NN	O	E_CLS
ให้	CC	O	B_CLS
หยุด	VV	O	I_CLS
ทำงาน	VV	O	I_CLS
ออกอากาศ	VV	O	I_CLS
รายการ	NN	O	I_CLS
โทรทัศน์	NN	O	E_CLS

จาก	PS	O	B_CLS
นั้น	AJ	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เจ้าหน้าที่	NN	O	I_CLS
ทีม	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
แมวดำ	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
ได้	AX	O	I_CLS
นำ	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
ไป	AV	O	I_CLS
ควบคุม	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	E_CLS
ที่	CC	O	B_CLS
เป็น	VV	O	I_CLS
ชาย	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จำนวน	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
78	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ไป	AV	O	I_CLS
คุมขัง	VV	O	I_CLS
ที่	PS	O	I_CLS
ประวีณ์นุช	NN	B_PER	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
และ	CC	O	B_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	I_CLS
หญิง	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
4	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ไป	AV	O	I_CLS
คุมขัง	VV	O	I_CLS
ยัง	AX	O	I_CLS
วิลดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
ต่อไป	AV	O	E_CLS

สำหรับ	PS	O	B_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	I_CLS
ทั้ง	AJ	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
82	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ประกอบ	VV	O	I_CLS
ด้วย	PS	O	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
องค์การ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
มีศรี	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
นเรศ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จินตะเวช	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
มณเฑียร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โรม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ณัฐพงษ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โตทวิวงศ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อรรถพล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ศรีผึ้ง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สรพัช	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ติชะวาณิชย์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ศักดิ์สิทธิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วิลาวัลย์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ฉัตร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
นันทภูษิตานนท์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
พงษ์มนู	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วิชัยกุล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วีระพล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
กำเนิดผล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
เจษฎา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ศรีก่อเกื้อ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สาธิต	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คุ้มไข่น้ำ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
กระแสร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คงอุดม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สรรพภัญญู	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ตันดิลกตระกูล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อัครนันท์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สมหมาย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
กันต์พงษ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ปราศจากศัตรู	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วุฒิพงศ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทองสุวรรณ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
พนิดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คลังแสง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วราวุธ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
หล่อประสงค์สุข	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ซูการ์โน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ลิ้มจิตรกร	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
พนม	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ภัทรประสิทธิ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
รังสิกร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อัศวรุ่งเรือง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุธรรม	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทิพยชล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ร่มธรรม	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ศิลปอาชา	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
กิตติศักดิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แทนทรัพย์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุวรรณา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
หลีนวรัตน์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
พิมพ์พิชชา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ดนตรีเสนาะ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สันต์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ลิ้มจิตรกร	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ษฐา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทองหนัก	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
บุญยิ่ง	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
กิตติธาราทรัพย์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
กาญจน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ชาญประดิษฐ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วรรณวิภา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เลาหพล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุรศักดิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บัณฑิตเทอดสกุล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุพัชรี	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
มะทา	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อภิชาติ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อุฬารกุล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ชัชวาล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แดงโชติ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ทวิวงศ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
กัณณ์กิตตินันท์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
เทียบจุฑา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ใจสำราญ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
จุติ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ไวยากรณ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
การณิก	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พชรทรัพย์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
พีระเดช	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เทพอักษรณรงค์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
จุฬาลักษณ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ช่างเหลา	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อนุชา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วริณวัชรโรจน์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อมรเทพ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
นิยะโมสถ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ไชยามพวาน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สะสมทรัพย์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ละออง	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สันตพันธุ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุทธิชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อิ่มวิเศษ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ศักดิ์ดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ฐิติพิทยา	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

น.ส.	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ศักดิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ตั้งมั่นก่อกิจ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ชาตรี	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จุลใส	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ภัณฑิล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เชื้อเมืองพาน	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
พัฒนา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วริณวัชรโรจน์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
บัญญัติ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ตีรสวัสดิชัย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ณัฐพงษ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ชัยวิรัตน์นุกูล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ณัฐพงศ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เทียนทอง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ไชยชนก	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ขาวทอง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ศักดิ์สิทธิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โชคชัยวัฒนากร	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
รังสิกร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เทพาคำ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สรวีย์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บัวบาน	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ปรีดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สมวงศ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
จุลพงศ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ศรีนอก	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ตรัยวรรธน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เอี่ยมสะอาด	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

น.ส.	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ชนินทร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คุ้มไข่น้ำ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
เชาวฤทธิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ชาลีรินทร์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วารุจ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ปรีดาสุทธิจิตต์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ชริน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พั้วช่วย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ถิรเดช	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทองสุวรรณ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อัครเดช	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วัชรสินธุ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วัชรพงศ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ช่างเหลา	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ผกามาศ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อรรณนพพร	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ธรรมนัส	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ประวีณวงศ์วุฒิ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อานุภาพ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
รจิตโรจน์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ฉัตร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จินตะเวช	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ฐิติกันต์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ผลอำนวย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ประมวล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ธรรมเพชร	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
พิมพ์ภัทรา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
กิตติสุนทรสกุล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

น.ส.	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
จุรินทร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จิตตกิจ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อนันต์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วิทยารักษ์สรรค์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ธีระชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ฤกษ์หร่าย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สิงหภณ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สมวงศ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS



