คน	NN	O	B_CLS
รัก	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
'	PU	O	I_CLS
วรรณิดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
'	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ห้าม	VV	O	I_CLS
พลาด	VV	O	E_CLS

จิราพร	NN	B_PER	B_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ยินดีสุข	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
ไป	VV	O	I_CLS
เพียง	AV	O	I_CLS
ร่างกาย	NN	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
แต่	CC	O	B_CLS
ได้	AX	O	I_CLS
ทิ้ง	VV	O	I_CLS
เสียง	NN	O	I_CLS
เพลง	NN	O	E_CLS
อัน	CC	O	B_CLS
ไพเราะ	VV	O	I_CLS
ไว้	AX	O	I_CLS
ให้	AX	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
แฟน	NN	O	I_CLS
เพลง	NN	O	I_CLS
ได้	AX	O	I_CLS
คิด	VV	O	I_CLS
ถึง	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ล่าสุด	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ห้าง	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
บิ๊กซี	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
เทศบาล	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
นคร	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
อุดรธานี	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ร่วมกับ	PS	O	I_CLS
อินเดีย	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ร่วม	VV	O	I_CLS
รำลึก	VV	O	I_CLS
ถึง	VV	O	I_CLS
ปัญญารัตน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พิมพะนิตย์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ผุด	VV	O	I_CLS
คอนเสิร์ต	NN	O	E_CLS
ที่	CC	O	B_CLS
แฟน	NN	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
จริง	VV	O	I_CLS
ห้าม	VV	O	I_CLS
พลาด	VV	O	E_CLS

"	PU	O	B_CLS
15	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปี	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อาสพลธ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เจริญศิลป์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
A	XX	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
Special	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
Tribute	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
by	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ร้าน	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
_	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
D	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
-	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
Wa	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
"	PU	O	E_CLS

คอนเสิร์ต	NN	O	B_CLS
ที่	CC	O	I_CLS
คุณ	PR	O	I_CLS
ต้อง	AX	O	I_CLS
พา	VV	O	I_CLS
แม่	NN	O	I_CLS
มา	AV	O	I_CLS
ดู	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
โดย	CC	O	I_CLS
ศิลปิน	NN	O	I_CLS
คุณภาพ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อาทิ	CC	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
กรวีร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จเด็ศ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วิทยารักษ์สรรค์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ซูการ์โน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สรรณ์ไตรภพ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สุทธิชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
-	PU	O	I_CLS
ศุภโชติ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ศุภปกรณ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
นพสิทธิ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกรียงไกร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เทพอักษรณรงค์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปวิตรา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พูนศรีธนากูล	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สฤษดิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จินา	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ธิษะณา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
-	PU	O	I_CLS
สุรพันธ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ตันติรัตนานนท์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
วิสุทธิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เสรีรักษ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
30	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
บท	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
เพลง	NN	E_MEA	I_CLS
ถูก	AX	O	I_CLS
ถ่ายทอด	VV	O	I_CLS
ให้	AX	O	I_CLS
ฟัง	VV	O	I_CLS
แน่	PR	O	I_CLS
ๆ	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
23	NU	B_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
พ.ค.	NN	E_DTM	I_CLS
นี้	AJ	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สำนักงาน	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
พระพุทธศาสนา	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
_	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
จ.	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
ลำปาง	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เพียง	AV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รอบ	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จอง	VV	O	I_CLS
บัตร	NN	O	I_CLS
ที่	CC	O	I_CLS
ศูนย์	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
วิทยาศาสตร์	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
การ	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
แพทย์	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ทุก	NU	O	I_CLS
สาขา	CL	O	E_CLS



